how2interactive.com 2015-02-16

# How 2 Interactive | Power your Ads with Information

Please read this policy to understand what information How2Interactive collects, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the use and sharing of your information when using the How2Interactive Advertising Solutions (H2) sites as a visitor. The H2 sites include sites that are branded "How2Network" and "How2Interactive" as well as sites on the following domains: How2Interactive.com, How2network.com.

**What this policy covers**  
This policy covers business contact information, such as name, email address, telephone number and address and other work-related information, that visitors provide to H2 online on publicly available H2 sites (where advertiser login is not required). If you are a business enrolled in advertiser programs that are subject to the Advertiser Master Services Terms and Conditions, Insertion Order(s) or other advertising or marketing agreements (collectively, "Advertising Agreement"), please refer to your Advertising Agreement to learn more about how How2Interactive may use information about your business. The terms of such business agreements supersede the provisions of this Privacy Policy. 

**Types of information we collect and how we use it**  
The following describes what information How2Interactive Advertising Solutions collects from visitors to the H2 sites as well as outside the How2Interactive network of web sites, and how we may use it: 

  1. **Email addresses and related information**  
There may be opportunities for visitors to the site to sign-up to receive email communications. Visitors may subscribe by providing an email address and other requested information. Recipients of email marketing messages will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from future messages via the link(s) provided within the message. 
  2. **Search**  
The Bid4keywords.com site offers web search functionality to visitors. Anonymous cookies are used on the site in connection with the search functionality. 
  3. **Cookies and web beacons on H2 web sites**  
How2Interactive accesses [How2Interactive domain cookies](http://www.vortal.com/privacy.html) and may use [How2Interactive web beacons](http://www.vortal.com/privacy.html) when you visit the H2 sites or other sites on the How2Interactive domain. How2Interactive and certain partners working on behalf of How2Interactive, also use web beacons on the H2 sites. How2Interactive may share site usage information about visitors to the H2 sites with third-party advertising companies for the purpose of targeting and measuring the effectiveness of our Internet advertisements on this site and other sites. For this purpose, How2Interactive and these third-party advertising companies note some of the pages you visit on our sites through the use of web beacons. 

The information collected by these third-party advertising companies through the use of these web beacons is not personally identifiable. For more information about our third-party advertisers, including how to opt out of their targeting programs, please visit their sites: [Omniture (207.net)](http://www.omniture.com/), [Doubleclick](http://www.doubleclick.com/), [Commission Junction](http://www.cj.com/) and [Performics](http://www.performics.com/). 

In addition to the above, How2Interactive' email delivery vendor may employ web beacons and cookies within HTML email messages sent on our behalf and on the H2 sites. The use of cookies and web beacons described above help How2Interactive to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use the H2 sites. 

  1. **H2 cookies and web beacons outside the How2Interactive network of web sites**  
How2Interactive Search Marketing offers advertisers tools that allow them to better understand the performance of their online marketing campaigns. For more information about these tools and the web beacons and cookies used, please read the [How2Interactive Search Marketing Tools Privacy Statement](http://www.vortal.com/privacy.html).
  2. **Promotions and sweepstakes**  
From time to time, How2Interactive may sponsor or host promotions and sweepstakes where we collect information. Use and sharing of this information will be disclosed in promotion and sweepstakes rules or on the page where you sign-up. 
  3. **IP addresses and information specific to your computer**  
SearchVortal logs IP information when you visit our sites, including the H2 sites. In addition to this information, How2Interactive collects information that your computer's browser automatically reports to us such as information about your operating system and browser version. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
How2Interactive does not rent, sell or share personally identifiable information about visitors to the H2 sites. However, How2Interactive may share this information with selected partners, vendors, agents or others who work on our behalf, in order to provide products or services you've requested, or when we have your permission. In addition, How2Interactive may share information about you if How2Interactive is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, How2Interactive will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Please note that we may also share information in the event that we are asked to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or as otherwise permitted by law. 

**Other**  
How2Interactive may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on this site. 

The H2 sites are not targeted at children and are not intended for use by children under the age of 13. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the following: 

How2Interactive.com  
c/o The How2Interactive Group PMB2399   
101 West 21rd St.   
New York, NY 10011   
917-400-4449 _        
_  
Effective Date: MAY 1, 2006
